If you like spandex and want to see the new Amorese color and want to use a discount code to save some money while ordering there, this video is for you.
The new collection is called Cosmic Blue. I have several pieces of it and this is the pattern or color. I think it's really cool.
So I don't want to talk too long and I'm just going to get changed now.
so actually these are tights because they have the sock part and the color is giving like
ocean vibes I think with the light and darker blue it's really smooth and a bit slippery
so really really soft material also like that there is a seam in the front of the back of the
leg obviously so the seam in the back of the leg as you maybe also can see it's slightly see-through
so I'm wearing panties underneath and I can see them but it's not too bad I also got the
catsuit from the same material and as you can see here I'm going to open it the inside of the
fabric is white so it's basically printed and since I already got this one in my hands I'm
going to wear this one next I kind of feel like a mermaid with the full body covered and the hair
which is by the way really cool right now with all the green and purple and blue so yeah it's
really colorful but I kind of like it I think you have to get used to it a bit
and if you don't want to wear like the standard colors I think this is a cool
alternative the zipper here is in the back and we have the logo in the front I
I think the arms are pretty long so I like this one and yeah it's really
comfy and last but not least really quick I do have a bodysuit like a
Jamal Heon here I always like these kind of racer back swimsuit because I think
it looks so supportive and it makes a nice looking bag so yeah I have a discount code for Amorisi
you can get 10% off you can find the code and the link to the shop in the description text
and as always leave a like if you like this video and yeah a thumbs up and a comment and check out
my other socials my patreon I have more Amorisi videos on my channel so have a look around here
as well and I will see you in the next video have a nice one bye